

# **HOLLIE NEWTON**

# **CONTACT INFO**



07526 395 191



h.newton@hotmail.co.uk



www.reclayaim.com



www.linkedin.com/in/hollie-newton-964071272



Preston, Lancashire.

# **EDUCATION**

Mar-Jun 2023

**CODING/SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT**Code Lancashire Bootcamp

2016-2019

**FDSC CANINE SCIENCE**Myerscough College (UCLan)

2009-2010

BTEC DIPLOMA ANIMAL STUDIES

Myerscough college

1999-2004

GCSE

Brownedge St Marys

# REFERENCES

**Dr. Amer Sheikh**Chief Data Scientist at Bearing
Point UK

Amersheik@gmail.com 07944905095

**Martina Austin** 

Director/Designer at The Pleasant Pheasant Co.

Design@thepleasantpheasant.net 07904161511

#### **PROFILE**

15 years experience running several successful businesses, with a passion for expanding my knowledge and an evolutionary mindset. Working remotely has brought great strengths such as self motivation, creative thinking, problem solving, and attention to detail. Each job has pushed for varied skill sets, which has taught me to adapt easily. Very much a people person with great communication, time management, and leadership ability. Having ADHD has been a superpower in producing my extremely creative flare and motivation for organisational skills.

## **EXPERIENCE**

MAR-JUN 2023 CODE LANCASHIRE **DIGITAL SKILLS BOOTCAMP STUDENT** 

12-week programme involving 80 hours of guided learning in group sessions covering Front/Back End, Fullstack, Frameworks, Data Science, Machine Learning. Individual

production of a Pokadex App.

Skills covered: HTML / CSS /Javascript / React / GitHub / Python / Next.js / SQL / Tailwind / Node.js / Jupyter

Notebook.

2019 - PRESENT RECLAYAIM **JEWELLER & ARTIST** 

Working with Precious Metals. Designing new collections. Production of orders with Time & Deadline Management, and Attention to Detail. Website Design/Social Media Management. Email Marketing. Account Keeping. Event Management: Planning & Participating in Country Shows (UK) to increase Business & Customer Networking.

2020 - 2021 THE BRITISH COUNTRY EMPORIUM **CO-DIRECTOR & CREATOR** 

Hosting & Collaborating alongside other Small Business Entrepreneurs to produce 'The British Country Emporium' - a place for all things small business & country. Social Media & Time Management. Communication and networking with like-minded businesses across the UK.

MAY 07 - AUG 20 DOG BEHAVIOURIST DOG TRAINER/DIRECTOR

A client base roll, involving problem solving ways to train dogs, and creative ways to teach owners. Structuring

plans and goals for individual client & canine

needs/requirements. Group training sessions provided team & project management skills. Keeping logs and

spreadsheets for each client.

## **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

Html	
css	
Javascript	
React	
Python	
Website Management	_
Social Media Management	_
Email Marketing	

#### PERSONAL SKILLS

Creative Thinker Communication
Attention to Detail Self Motivated

f Motivated Leadership

Project Management

Working Remotely

Problem Solver Time Management